A Finding Aid to the Holger Cahill Papers, 1910-1993, bulk 1910-1960, in the Archives of American Art
Archives of American Art
- Works Progress Administration Federal Art Project, 1934-1970; Series 3; Archival Resource Key; 10.75 Linear feet Boxes 2-14, 18, MMs009
  - Administration of the State WPA/FAP, 1935-1943; 3.4; Archival Resource Key
    - Illinois, Millar's Chicago Letter, 1940; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5289, Frame 1071-1082)
    - Iowa, A Guide to Dubuque, 1937; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5289, Frame 1083-1103)
    - Iowa, [ Sioux City Community Federal Art Center], 1938; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5289, Frame 1104-1114)
    - Iowa, Information and Reports on the Two Hemisphere Band Chariot, 1938; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5289, Frame 1115-1143)
    - Louisiana, Report by Gideon T. Stanton, undated; Archival Resource Key; (1 of 2) (Reel 5289, Frame 1144-1146)
    - Louisiana, Report by Gideon T. Stanton, undated; Archival Resource Key; (2 of 2) (Reel 5289, Frame 1149-1152)
    - Louisiana, Statement by Dr. Robert E. Plunkett, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5289, Frame 1147-1148)
    - Louisiana, New Orleans: What To See, How To See It, 1935; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5289, Frame 1153-1154)
    - Louisiana, Afton Villa, 1935; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5289, Frame 1155-1163)
    - Louisiana, Report of Federal Art Project of Louisiana as of, May 1, 1939; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5289, Frame 1164-1169)
    - Michigan, Untitled Report, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5289, Frame 1170-1184)
    - Michigan, Michigan School for the Blind Receives Sculpture by WPA Artists, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5289, Frame 1185)
    - Michigan, Lincoln by Samuel Cashwan, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5289, Frame 1186)
    - Michigan, The Puppets of the Lano Family, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5289, Frame 1187-1189)
    - Michigan, Fredenthal Murals in the Detroit Naval Armory, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5289, Frame 1190-1192)
    - Michigan, Edgar Yaeger's Murals in the Detroit Naval Armory, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5289, Frame 1193-1194)
    - Michigan, Royal Oak High School Receives Mural Panel by the Makielski Brothers, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5289, Frame 1195-1196)
    - Michigan, Exhibition Press Releases, Index of American Design, 1937-1938; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5289, Frame 1197-1201)
    - Michigan, Report on Art Projects for Unemployment Relief in Michigan, 1935-1942 by Paul McPharlin, Archival Resource Key (Reel 5289, Frame 1202-1237)
    - Minnesota, Minnesota Artist, 1939; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5289, Frame 1238-1251)
    - Minnesota, [ Walker Art Center], 1940; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5289, Frame 1252-1283)
    - Missouri, Press Release, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5289, Frame 1284-1289)
    - Missouri, People's Art Service Center, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5289, Frame 1290-1292)
    - Missouri, Work Projects Administration Service Division - Missouri, Accomplishment Report, February 1, 1943; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5289, Frame 1293-1335)
    - Nebraska, Nebraska Folklore: Pioneer Recollections, 1940; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5289, Frame 1336-1349)
    - New Jersey, Program Operation Report, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5289, Frame 1350-1360)
    - New Jersey, The Williamsburg Housing and Newark Airport Projects by Burgoyne Diller, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5289, Frame 1361-1362)
    - New Mexico, Spanish Colonial Arts in New Mexico by R. Vernon Hunter, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5289, Frame 1363-1380)
    - New York, American Artists Face the Future, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5289, Frame 1381-1395)
    - New York, Statistical Report of the Art Teaching Project, 1936; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5289, Frame 1396)
    - New York, Federal Art Centers of New York, circa 1938; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5289, Frame 1414-1433)
    - New York, A Community Art Center for Harlem, circa 1938; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5289, Frame 1434-1445)
    - New York, Recent Prints Available for Allocation, circa 1938; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5289, Frame 1446-1454)
    - New York, Descriptions of Paintings from the Art and Psychopathology Exhibition, 1938; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5289, Frame 1397-1413)
    - New York, Free Guided Tours, 1938; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5289, Frame 1455-1458)
    - New York, Art Work in Non-Federal Buildings and the Federal Art Project of the City of New York, circa 1939; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5289, Frame 1459-1473)
    - New York, Art Caravan Report, April-May 1939; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5289, Frame 1474-1488)
    - New York, Art Caravan Report, cont., April-May 1939; Archival Resource Key; (includes photos of Art Caravan) (Reel 5290, Frame 0004-0077)
    - New York, Art Caravan Report, June-August 1939; Archival Resource Key; (includes photos of Art Caravan) (Reel 5290, Frame 0078-0161)
    - New York, Record of Program Operation and Accomplishment, 1943; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5290, Frame 0162-0185)
    - North Carolina, The WPA and Winston-Salem Art Center, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5290, Frame 0186-0189)
    - North Carolina, Manual of Operation and Procedure of North Carolina Federal Art Projects, 1936-1937; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5290, Frame 0190-0209)
    - North Carolina, Report on the Preservation of Mountain Culture in Great Smoky Mountains National Park by Dr. Hans Huth, 1941; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5290, Frame 0210-0244)
    - Ohio, Cleveland Museum of Art, Eductional Work with High Schools, circa 1933; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5290, Frame 0245-0249)
    - Ohio, Cleveland Museum of Art, Educational Functions of an Art Museum, 1933; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5290, Frame 0250-0253)
    - Ohio, Cleveland Museum of Art, Museum Educational Work for the General Public, 1939; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5290, Frame 0254-0256)
    - Ohio, Cleveland Museum of Art, The Art Museum and the Secondary School, circa 1940; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5290, Frame 0257-0267)
    - Ohio, Cleveland Museum of Art, Visual Material Available for Use in Secondary Schools, 1940; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5290, Frame 0268-0312)
    - Ohio, Cleveland Museum of Art, Report on Work with Shaker Heights Secondary Schools, 1940; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5290, Frame 0313-0398)
    - Oklahoma, Record of Program Operation and Accomplishment, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5290, Frame 0399-0405)
    - Oklahoma, Report by Nan Sheets, 1936; Archival Resource Key; (includes photo of Sheets) (Reel 5290, Frame 0406-0409)
    - Oregon, Report on Salem Federal Art Center, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5290, Frame 0410-0421)
    - Oregon, Art in Timberline Lodge by E. J. Griffith, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5290, Frame 0422-0423)
    - Oregon, The Problem of Gallery Attendants by Charles Val Clear, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5290, Frame 0424-0429)
    - Oregon, WPA Community Art Centers, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5290, Frame 0430-0435)
    - Pennsylvania, Report on the Subject of Ornamental Cast Iron in Philadelphia in the First Half of the 19th Century by Katherine Milhous, 1936; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5290, Frame 0436-0455)
    - Pennsylvania, The Harmony Society in Pennsylvania, 1937; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5290, Frame 0456-0476)
    - Pennsylvania, Defense Work in Progress, 1941; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5290, Frame 0477-0478)
    - Virginia, Memoranda on Community Art Centers, circa 1938; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5290, Frame 0479-0504)
    - Washington State, Bulletin of the Spokane Art Center, 1939; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5290, Frame 0517-0525)
    - Wisconsin, Artist Who Painted Pope Pius XI Makes Show Place of Old Barn, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5290, Frame 0527-0530)
    - Wisconsin, Miscellaneous Publicity and Notes from Press Digest, 1937, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5290, Frame 0531-0534)
    - Wisconsin, Notes on and Statements by Wisconsin Artists, 1939; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5290, Frame 0535-0545)
    - Wisconsin, Record of Program Operation and Accomplishment, 1942; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5290, Frame 0546-0574)
    - Wyoming, A Review of the Federal Art Galleries in Wyoming by E. E. Lowry, 1938; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5290, Frame 0575-0582)
  - Meeting Minutes and Transcripts, 1936-1941; 3.5; Archival Resource Key
    This subseries contains minutes and transcripts of WPA/FAP meetings and conferences, arranged chronologically.
    - Planning Program of Work and Travel Conference, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1105, Frame 0553-0556)
    - Regional and State Directors Conference, September 1936; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1105, Frame 0533-0541)
    - Fogg Museum Meeting, January 20, 1938; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5288, Frame 0003-0026)
    - Federal Art Directors Conference, Washington, D.C., May 1938; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5292, Frame 0404-0440)
    - Annual Meeting of the American Handicraft Council, February 1940; Archival Resource Key (Reel NDA 15, Frame 0990-0994)
    - Community Service Projects Meeting, May 21-23, 1940; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1105, Frame 0518-0532)
    - Community Service Projects Meeting, May 29, 1940; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5288, Frame 0048-0051)
    - Art Supervisors Conference, Washington, D.C., January 1941; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5288, Frame 0052-0064)
    - Conference on the Arts Program of the WPA, Transcript, Part 1, October-November 1941; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1105, Frame 0785-0866)
    - Conference on the Arts Program of the WPA, Transcript, Part 2, October-November 1941; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1105, Frame 0867-0904)
    - Conference on the Arts Program of the WPA, Transcript, Part 3, October-November 1941; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1105, Frame 0905-0974)
  - Allocations, 1935-1943, 1970; 3.6; Archival Resource Key
    This subseries documents financial allotments for the FAP program on a national and state level. It contains chronologically arranged correspondence and memoranda showing total allocations and containing lists breaking down allotments by state, as well as general correspondence related to allocations.
    Allocation control cards were produced by the FAP's graphic arts division as a record of prints received in, and distributed by, the FAP's office in Washington D.C. for allocation and exhibition purposes. They give a number indicating the exhibition in which each print was included and a number indicating the total number of prints received (see General Correspondence, 1970, in this subseries). The cards are organized alphabetically by state.
    Also found here are tables of financial allotment statistics, printed material related to allocations of art work and a notebook entitled Congressional and D.C. Allocations.
    - Allocation Control Cards, California, circa 1935-1941; Archival Resource Key; (1 of 2) (Reel 1106, Frame 1093-1186)
    - Allocation Control Cards, California, circa 1935-1941; Archival Resource Key; (2 of 2) (Reel 1106, Frame 1274-1279)
    - Allocation Control Cards, Colorado, circa 1935-1941; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1106, Frame 1187-1190)
    - Allocation Control Cards, Connecticut, circa 1935-1941; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1106, Frame 1191-1193)
    - Allocation Control Cards, Florida, circa 1935-1941; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1106, Frame 1194-1195)
    - Allocation Control Cards, Illinois, circa 1935-1941; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1106, Frame 1196-1217)
    - Allocation Control Cards, Kansas, circa 1935-1941; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1106, Frame 1218-1219)
    - Allocation Control Cards, Louisiana, circa 1935-1941; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1106, Frame 1220-1221)
    - Allocation Control Cards, Massachusetts, circa 1935-1941; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1106, Frame 1222-1250)
    - Allocation Control Cards, Michigan, circa 1935-1941; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1106, Frame 1251-1259)
    - Allocation Control Cards, Minnesota, circa 1935-1941; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1106, Frame 1260-1266)
    - Allocation Control Cards, New Hampshire, circa 1935-1941; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1106, Frame 1267-1269)
    - Allocation Control Cards, New Mexico, circa 1935-1941; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1106, Frame 1270-1272)
    - Allocation Control Cards, New York, circa 1935-1941; Archival Resource Key; (1 of 2) (Reel 1106, Frame 1273)
    - Allocation Control Cards, New York, circa 1935-1941; Archival Resource Key; (2 of 2) (Reel 1106, Frame 1280-1419)
    - Allocation Control Cards, Ohio, circa 1935-1941; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1106, Frame 1420-1454)
    - Allocation Control Cards, Oregon, circa 1935-1941; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1106, Frame 1455-1456)
    - Allocation Control Cards, Pennsylvania, circa 1935-1941; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1106, Frame 1457-1492)
    - Allocation Control Cards, Rhode Island, circa 1935-1941; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1106, Frame 1493-1495)
    - Allocation Control Cards, Utah, circa 1935-1941; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1106, Frame 1496-1497)
    - Allocation Control Cards, Washington, circa 1935-1941; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1106, Frame 1498-1506)
    - Allocation Control Cards, Wisconsin, circa 1935-1941; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1106, Frame 1507-1512)
    - Allocation Statistics, 1935-1937; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1106, Frame 1061-1090)
    - Allocations to States, 1935; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1106, Frame 0875-0899)
    - Allocations to States, January-March 1936; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1106, Frame 0900-0931)
    - Allocations to States, April 1936; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1106, Frame 0932-0958)
    - Allocations to States, May-June 1936; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1106, Frame 0959-0989)
    - Allocations to States, July 1936; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1106, Frame 0990-1029)
    - Allocations to States, July 1936-January 1937; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1106, Frame 1030-1060)
    - Commercial Standards for Artists' Oil Paints, 1939; Archival Resource Key (Reel NDA 15, Frame 0668-0681)
    - Commercial Standards for Artists' Oil Paints, 1941-1943; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1106, Frame 0675-0704)
    - General Correspondence, 1936-1943; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1106, Frame 0655-0674)
    - General Correspondence, 1970; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1106, Frame 1092)
    - Notebook, Congressional and D.C. Allocations, 1936-1941; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1106, Frame 0705-0803)
    - Printed Material, 1936-1939; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1106, Frame 0804-0874)
  - Community Art Centers, 1934-1946; 3.7; Archival Resource Key
    This subseries includes reports on various community art centers and news clippings about the art center in Curry County, Oregon.
    - News Clippings, Curry County Art Center, 1939-1941; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1107, Frame 0342-0382)
    - Reports, 1934; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1107, Frame 0220-0221)
    - Reports, circa 1935-1941; Archival Resource Key; (1 of 2) (Reel 1107, Frame 0160-0204)
    - Reports, circa 1935-1941; Archival Resource Key; (2 of 2) (Reel 1107, Frame 0214-0219)
    - Reports, 1936; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1107, Frame 0222-0283)
    - Reports, 1937-1938; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1107, Frame 0284-0322)
    - Reports, 1938; Archival Resource Key; (1 of 2) (Reel 1107, Frame 0205-0213)
    - Reports, 1938; Archival Resource Key; (2 of 2) (Reel NDA 15, Frame 0866-0872)
    - Reports, 1939-1946; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1107, Frame 0323-0340)
  - FAP Divisions, 1935-1940; 3.8; Archival Resource Key
    This subseries documents the activities of FAP divisions through typescripts, an interview transcript, memoranda, printed material and copies of poster designs.
    Art teaching typescripts include the following: Jacksonville Negro Art Gallery, Florida, Children's Art Gallery, Washington, D.C., Art and the Problem Child, Child Art Teaching, Saturday Morning Classes at the Kalamazoo Institute of Arts, Information Concerning District of Columbia Children's Drawings in Big Stone Gap Exhibition, The Artist Teaches, The Functions of Art Teaching in Education, The Works Program, and Child Art.
    Records relating to murals include a biographical sketch of the architect William Lescaze; a typescript entitled Statistical Note on Murals; and a booklet entitled Historical Murals in the Los Angeles County Hall of Records Board of Supervisors' Hearing Room. Records relating to posters include a typescript entitled List of Visual Aid and Other Training Material Produced for Military Establishments by Missouri Graphics Phase Units, 28 copies of poster designs, and a photograph of men in a poster composition room.
    - Art Teaching, 1936-1939; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1107, Frame 0738-0798)
    - Crafts, 1940; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1107, Frame 0799-0804)
    - Design Laboratory, 1935-1936; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1107, Frame 0805-0809)
    - Graphic Art, 1940; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1107, Frame 0810-0866)
    - Murals, 1936-1939; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1107, Frame 0867-0906)
    - Posters, circa 1935-1940; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1107, Frame 0907-0977)
  - Index of American Design, 1936-1947; 3.9; Archival Resource Key
    The purpose of the Index of American Design was to compile a pictorial record of objects in the decorative, applied and folk arts, particularly objects of American origin. This subseries includes correspondence, memoranda, manuals, reports, typescripts, press releases, state reports primarily concerning Illinois projects, exhibition loan records, printed material and photographs of exhibitions and artwork, documenting that endeavor.
    Articles and reports include documents and manuals describing the form and function of the Index, and outlining related procedures to be followed. They also include typescripts about the Index including Recording American Design, [ The Shaker Portfolio], The Derivation and History of Weathervanes, A Short History of the Weathervane, The Eagle in American Design, American Traditions for Young People, and Notes on American Carvers and Carving. Also found here are press releases, notes, a list of collectors, memoranda, Art Circular No. 3 and a reprint entitled American Popular Art as Recorded in the Index of American Design by Erwin O. Christensen.
    Photographs include a bound portfolio of photographs of index plates representing artist renderings of Illinois objects, and a series of photographs depicting the process of making an index plate.
    - Articles and Reports, circa 1936-1941; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1107, Frame 1075-1234)
    - Articles and Reports, 1936; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1107, Frame 1235-1285)
    - Articles and Reports, 1937; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1107, Frame 1286-1310)
    - Articles and Reports, 1938; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1107, Frame 1311-1396)
    - Articles and Reports, 1941, 1947; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1107, Frame 1397-1412)
    - Correspondence and Memoranda, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1107, Frame 0979-0985)
    - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1936; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1107, Frame 0993-1058)
    - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1937, 1940; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1107, Frame 1059-1068)
    - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1941-1942; Archival Resource Key; (1 of 2) (Reel 1107, Frame 1069-1074)
    - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1941-1942; Archival Resource Key; (2 of 2) (Reel 1107, Frame 0986-0992)
    - Lists of Artwork/Receipts for Exhibition Loans, 1936; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5292, Frame 0683-0730)
    - Notes, circa 1936-1942; Archival Resource Key; (1 of 2) (Reel 1108, Frame 0263-0304)
    - Notes, circa 1936-1942; Archival Resource Key; (2 of 2) (Reel 5292, Frame 0672-0682)
    - State Reports, 1942; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1107, Frame 1413-1438)
    - State Reports, Illinois, 1942; Archival Resource Key; (1 of 2) (Reel 1107, Frame 1439-1503)
    - State Reports, Illinois, 1942; Archival Resource Key; (2 of 2) (Reel 1108, Frame 0001-0262)
    - Portfolio of Index Plates from Illinois, 1942; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1108, Frame 0554-0938)
    - Printed Material, Booklet The Silkscreen Process, 1941; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1108, Frame 0508-0553)
    - Photographs, Exhibitions, 1938-1939; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1108, Frame 0305-0328)
    - Photographs, "Making an Index Plate,", circa 1936-1942; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1108, Frame 0367-0423)
    - Photographs, Objects, circa 1936-1942; Archival Resource Key; (1 of 3) (Reel 1108, Frame 0329-0366)
    - Photographs, Objects, circa 1936-1942; Archival Resource Key; (2 of 3) (Reel 1108, Frame 0424-0491)
    - Photographs, Objects, circa 1936-1942; Archival Resource Key; (3 of 3) (Reel 1108, Frame 0506-0507)
    - Photographs, Shaker Buildings and People, circa 1936-1942; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1108, Frame 0492-0505)
  - Exhibitions, 1935-1942; 3.10; Archival Resource Key
    This subseries consists of reports on exhibitions, shipping receipts for artwork, news clippings, exhibition catalogs, and records relating to the FAP Exhibition of Contemporary Art at the 1939-1940 New York World's Fair.
    Records of the New York World'd Fair exhibition include correspondence, typescripts, memoranda, a budget plan, a list of sculptors employed by the FAP in New York City, prospectuses for artists, a calendar of events, press releases, printed material and photographs.
    - Catalogs, 1936-1939; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1107, Frame 584-683)
    - Childrens' Art Exhibitions, 1937-1939; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1107, Frame 539-563)
    - New York World's Fair Exhibition (1939-1940), 1935-1938; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5292, Frame 0732-0778)
    - New York World's Fair Exhibition (1939-1940), 1938-1939; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5292, Frame 0780-0839)
    - New York World's Fair Exhibition (1939-1940), Archival Resource Key (Reel 5292, Frame 0841-0888)
    - New York World's Fair Exhibition (1939-1940), Archival Resource Key (Reel 5292, Frame 0890-0950)
    - New York World's Fair Exhibition (1939-1940), Archival Resource Key (Reel 1107, Frame 564-583)
    - Exhibition Reports, 1936-1942; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1107, Frame 509-538)
    - News Clippings, 1936-1939; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1107, Frame 684-700)
  - Other New Deal Art Projects, 1935-1942; 3.11; Archival Resource Key
    This subseries contains records related to two other New Deal art projects: the Office of Emergency Management (OEM) Art Project and the Treasury Department Art Project (TDAP). Included here are one bulletin relating to the former and four letters and a series of bulletins relating to the latter.
    - OEM Art Bulletin No.1, 1942; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1109, Frame 1068-1069)
    - TDAP Correspondence, 1935; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1109, Frame 1014-1022)
    - TDAP Bulletin No. 1, March 1, 1935; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5290, Frame 0583-0595)
    - TDAP Bulletin No. 2, April 1, 1935; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5290, Frame 0596-0609)
    - TDAP Bulletin No. 3, May-June 1935; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5290, Frame 0610-0625)
    - TDAP Bulletin No. 4, July-August 1935; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5290, Frame 0626-0641)
    - TDAP Bulletin No. 5, September 1935; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5290, Frame 0642-0662)
    - TDAP Bulletin No. 6, October-November 1935; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5290, Frame 0663-0678)
    - TDAP Bulletin No. 7, December 1935; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5290, Frame 0679-0696)
    - TDAP Bulletin No. 8, January-February 1936; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5290, Frame 0697-0732)
    - TDAP Bulletin No. 9, March-May 1936; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5290, Frame 0733-0756)
    - TDAP Bulletin No. 10, June-August 1936; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5290, Frame 0757-0776)